<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2021-06-07T17:05:17+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Rafid Muqsith</title><subtitle>Welcome! This site is intentionally created to show my portfolio, but maybe I'll post other things as well.
</subtitle><author><name>Rafid Muqsith</name><email>rafidmuqsith@gmail.com</email></author><entry><title type="html">Brutal Boss Battle</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/bbb" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Brutal Boss Battle" /><published>2021-06-07T14:43:00+07:00</published><updated>2021-06-07T14:43:00+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/bbb</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/bbb">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/fulls/bbb1.png&quot; class=&quot;fit image&quot; /&gt;
     Brutal Boss Battle (BBB) as you can tell is a 3D Boss Fighting Game, implementing simple AI with a decision tree as the base. This game was created for a group campus project in 2018. The game design was made by the whole group member. For the individual role, I work on the UX and UI assets. I designed the screen interface, where, when, and how things should be placed or show, and what color to use. &lt;br /&gt;
     The goal of this game is fairly simple. Player must defeat the boss, Rashon, while trying not to get out of the arena. Player can move, jump, and swing their sword to attack. The player doesn’t have hp but in exchange it will get thrown away if Rashon hits the player, with skill or Melee Attack. So player must dodge to avoid being thrown away and lose the game.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/fulls/bbb.gif&quot; class=&quot;fit image&quot; /&gt;  &lt;br /&gt;
    The arena of the fight will collapse as player progressively play the game. While fighting Rashon, he will first check if his skill (ground hit with red ground ripple effect) is ready or not, if yes, then he will use his skill,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/fulls/bbb3.png&quot; class=&quot;fit image&quot; /&gt;
    if not, then he will check if the character is in his Attack Range or not, if yes, he will start using Melee Attack, else he will start walking towards Player. When Rashon hp hit 30% it will trigger the enraged state, in which it has higher armor so it is hard to kill.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/fulls/bbb4.png&quot; class=&quot;fit image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The repo of the game can be found 
&lt;a href=&quot;#&quot; onclick=&quot;window.open('https://github.com/lokerz/BBB', '_blank')&quot; class=&quot;6u 12u(small)&quot;&gt;here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Rafid Muqsith</name><email>rafidmuqsith@gmail.com</email></author><category term="Portfolio" /><summary type="html"> Brutal Boss Battle (BBB) as you can tell is a 3D Boss Fighting Game, implementing simple AI with a decision tree as the base. This game was created for a group campus project in 2018. The game design was made by the whole group member. For the individual role, I work on the UX and UI assets. I designed the screen interface, where, when, and how things should be placed or show, and what color to use.  The goal of this game is fairly simple. Player must defeat the boss, Rashon, while trying not to get out of the arena. Player can move, jump, and swing their sword to attack. The player doesn’t have hp but in exchange it will get thrown away if Rashon hits the player, with skill or Melee Attack. So player must dodge to avoid being thrown away and lose the game.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">About Me</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/about-me" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="About Me" /><published>2021-04-14T21:37:44+07:00</published><updated>2021-04-14T21:37:44+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/aboutme</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/about-me">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/fulls/01.jpg&quot; class=&quot;fit image&quot; /&gt;
     Hello! my name is Muhammad Rafid Muqsith I’m an Minangnese, born in
    Pekanbaru and raised in Tangerang. Since childhood I moved several times,
    there are quite a number of places that I’ve moved to. Even so I have a
    hard time memorizing also remembering the when, the what, and especially the where (le kind of person who gets lost without a map :D). However, it got me used to adapting and it made me
    love to try out things.&lt;br /&gt;
     My current interest is Game Development particularly in Level
    Design. I’m also having a go at the Unreal Engine with its Blueprint and
    C++ for personal projects. I enjoy art too. Previously I had some
    experience in shooting and editing photos as well as videos. For the
    moment I’m learning about 3d modeling and animating.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Rafid Muqsith</name><email>rafidmuqsith@gmail.com</email></author><category term="About" /><summary type="html"> Hello! my name is Muhammad Rafid Muqsith I’m an Minangnese, born in Pekanbaru and raised in Tangerang. Since childhood I moved several times, there are quite a number of places that I’ve moved to. Even so I have a hard time memorizing also remembering the when, the what, and especially the where (le kind of person who gets lost without a map :D). However, it got me used to adapting and it made me love to try out things.  My current interest is Game Development particularly in Level Design. I’m also having a go at the Unreal Engine with its Blueprint and C++ for personal projects. I enjoy art too. Previously I had some experience in shooting and editing photos as well as videos. For the moment I’m learning about 3d modeling and animating.</summary></entry></feed>