<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2022-01-13T14:04:52+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Rafid Muqsith</title><subtitle>Welcome! This site is intentionally created to show my portfolio, but maybe I'll post other things as well.
</subtitle><author><name>Rafid Muqsith</name><email>rafidmuqsith@gmail.com</email></author><entry><title type="html">About Me</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/about-me" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="About Me" /><published>2021-04-14T21:37:44+07:00</published><updated>2021-04-14T21:37:44+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/aboutme</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/about-me">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/fulls/01.jpg&quot; class=&quot;fit image&quot; /&gt;
     Hello! my name is Muhammad Rafid Muqsith I’m an Minangnese, born in
    Pekanbaru and raised in Tangerang. Since childhood I moved several times,
    there are quite a number of places that I’ve moved to. Even so I have a
    hard time memorizing also remembering the when, the what, and especially the where (le kind of person who gets lost without a map :D). However, it got me used to adapting and it made me
    love to try out things.&lt;br /&gt;
     My current interest is Game Development particularly in Level
    Design. I’m also having a go at the Unreal Engine with its Blueprint and
    C++ for personal projects. I enjoy art too. Previously I had some
    experience in shooting and editing photos as well as videos. For the
    moment I’m learning about 3d modeling and animating.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Rafid Muqsith</name><email>rafidmuqsith@gmail.com</email></author><category term="About" /><summary type="html"> Hello! my name is Muhammad Rafid Muqsith I’m an Minangnese, born in Pekanbaru and raised in Tangerang. Since childhood I moved several times, there are quite a number of places that I’ve moved to. Even so I have a hard time memorizing also remembering the when, the what, and especially the where (le kind of person who gets lost without a map :D). However, it got me used to adapting and it made me love to try out things.  My current interest is Game Development particularly in Level Design. I’m also having a go at the Unreal Engine with its Blueprint and C++ for personal projects. I enjoy art too. Previously I had some experience in shooting and editing photos as well as videos. For the moment I’m learning about 3d modeling and animating.</summary></entry></feed>